scrippsnews.com 2014-07-29

# Privacy Policy | JTeach.org

Thank you for visiting the Board of Jewish Education of Metropolitan Chicago’s (BJE) website, JTeach.org and reviewing our privacy policy. The BJE does not collect your personal information when you visit our website unless you choose to provide that information to us. The BJE does not sell, exchange, or release your personally identifiable information to outside parties.

If You Send Us Personal Information  
BJE’s JTeach.org website only will collect personal information which you knowingly and voluntarily provide by, for example, sending emails, completing membership forms, registering for accounts, responding to surveys or ordering merchandise.  If you provide us with personal information, we normally will respond to your inquiry, request, or order.  
When we send you information by email, you always will have an immediate opportunity to decline further communication. Please use the contact specified in the email so that we can remove you from the list that contains your name. If you are uncertain about whom to contact, you may contact us at marshallcenter@bjechicago.org.

Information Collected and Stored Automatically  
If you visit our website, we automatically gather and store the following information about your visit so that we can track the use of our website in order to make improvements. This information is stored and used in aggregate form only, and is not used to contact you personally:  
The IP address from which you access our website  
The name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you are connecting from an America Online account)  
The type of browser and operating system used to access our website  
The date and time you access our site  
The pages, files, documents and links that you visit  
The Internet address of the website from which you linked to this website

Cookies  
In addition to information collected automatically, we use cookies, which are small pieces of information sent to your browser by a website that you visit. These cookies do not collect personally identifiable information. Cookies are used to track usage patterns, traffic trends, and customer behavior, as well as to record other information from the website. When you register on the website, cookies also allow us to save information so that you will not have to re-enter it the next time you visit. Many content adjustments and customer service improvements are made based on the data derived from cookies. Information that we collect from cookies will not be used to create profiles of users and will only be used in aggregate form.  
The BJE’s JTeach.org privacy policy does not cover any use of information that third parties may have collected from you (e.g., type of browser, operating system, domain name, day and time of visit, page(s) visited) or the methods used by the third-parties to collect that information (e.g., cookies, web beacons).

Children and Privacy  
Childrens’ Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance  
BJE is concerned about protecting children’s privacy. We do not collect personally identifiable information from children. If a visitor known to be a child (under the age of thirteen (13)) sends an email to JTeach.org, we only will use it to respond to the writer and not to create profiles or otherwise retain the information.

Security  
We take reasonable precautions to ensure that all credit card transactions that occur on the JTeach.org website are secure. When you submit your credit card for any purchase, that transaction is encrypted using “Secure Socket Layer” (SSL) encryption to protect your credit card information.  We monitor network traffic to ensure that our site remains available to all users and to identify unauthorized attempts to access, upload or change information or otherwise cause damage.  
Unauthorized access is prohibited and punishable under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and the National Information Infrastructure Protection Act.

Comments  
Questions and comments about this Privacy Policy may be directed to us via email at marshallcenter@bjechicago.org .  
This policy was last modified on July 9, 2014.
